nfieldmr.com 2015-10-04

# Privacy policy - NIPO Software

### _This privacy policy does NOT apply to respondents who have completed or are about to complete a market research survey on one of our products. For the privacy policy relevant to such surveys you should contact the market research company that has asked you to complete the survey._

### When and what information do we collect?

Your personal data is collected when you complete and submit a contact form, when you sent us an email or when you speak to us over the telephone. In particular, NIPO Software will collect and hold details of your name, address, email address, telephone number, (including mobile number), fax number, any information that you provide to us and any other personal information disclosed by you. Any information you provide to us will be treated with care and respect. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our website, you may send us an email at the address indicated in the contact us section.

### What do we do with your personal information?

By submitting a contact form you consent to us using the personal data contained in the form to provide you with information about NIPO Software products and services. Such information may include product offers, product launches, invites to seminars or to exhibitions or NIPO Software workshops, newsletters, e-newsletters, articles, industry analysis as well as general responses to any other information which you may have requested. In addition, you consent to us occasionally contacting you (including by telephone) to notify you about new information or services which we think you may find interesting or valuable.

By completing our job application forms in the job opportunity section of our site, you consent to us keeping your personal information on file for the purpose of considering your candidacy for a current employment opportunity with NIPO Software and/or to contact you if a future position matches your profile. If we believe that you may be a suitable candidate for a current or future position, we may contact you by phone, email or postal mail to discuss your interest in working at NIPO Software and/or to invite you to a job interview.

### With whom will we share your information?

NIPO Software will not share your personal information with other parties. Your personally identifiable information may however be transferred if NIPO Software is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets.

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information in the rare but possible circumstance that the information is subject to disclosure pursuant to judicial or other government subpoenas, warrants, orders or for similar legal or regulatory requirements.

### Contacting us

Please notify us by email to info@niposoftware.com if you: (a) do not wish your personal data to be used in the manner described before (we will be grateful if you set out your specific objections to any use); (b) wish to see the personal data we hold about you. We will endeavor to respond to your access request within 30 days of receiving your request. Of course, if the personal information we hold about you is inaccurate, incomplete or irrelevant, we shall correct or delete it after discussing the matter with you.
